## **Alvin Tsang**

(437) 268-3601 | alvinbno@gmail.com | Toronto, ON

### **Summary**

I am a Front-End Developer with over 3 years of experience creating and designing amazing websites for various clients and businesses using HTML, CSS, Javascript, jQuery, React, Angular, Node.js, Bootstrap, Material UI, MongoDB, MySQL, ASP.NET MVC, C#, RESTful APIs, and other web technologies. I want to create beautiful, user-friendly, high-performance websites that bring value and satisfaction to end users.

LinkedIn | Portfolio | Github

#### **Experience**

### AAS Education Consultancy | Hong Kong Web Developer (Freelance) | 09/2019 - Present

- Modernized design and mobile responsive web layout with Bootstrap 5, HTML, CSS, Javascript
- Optimized webpage loading speed by 25% using AWS CloudFront
- · Generated informative charts and graphs for the team leader using Power BI and Google Data Studio with ZohoCRM data
- · Proficient in using Git rebase for history cleanup and branch updates, leading to a more coherent commit history

# Rich Fame International Limited | Hong Kong Web Developer | 08/2022 - 02/2023

- Built a single web page of a cargo online application system for internal use to replace hand-written legacy to store shipment details using React, Redux, Ant Design, CSS
- Maintain Wordpress website using PHP 7.2, Wordpress 6.1.1, WP Engine by ensuring uptime, fixing bugs and modifying custom theme
- Involved and built a webpage for a Product management system (PMS) using Vue and PHP 5.6
- Integrate RESTful APIs for data retrieval and manipulation within Vue and React applications

### Flexsystem | Hong Kong Full Stack Programmer | 05/2021 - 08/2022

- Revamped an existing Angular 1.5 web application to Angular 11 in production for esteemed clients, including the Agricultural Bank of China, HKEAA, Great Eagle, and R&D initiatives
- · Maintained Angular web applications using Angular, Bootstrap 4, C#, and ISAM
- Responsible for building the web layout of a Customer Relationship Management (CRM) using ASP.NET MVC 5, HTML, CSS, jQuery and Entity Framework
- Modernized design and reduced bugs on many Angular widgets
- Implementing CSS3 Grid and Flexbox layouts to create complex and responsive page designs

### **Skills**

Angular, React.js, Tailwind, Material UI, Typescript, CSS, jQuery, ASP.NET MVC, Node.js, RESTful APIs, MongoDB, MySQL, EC2, S3, CloudFront, Git

### **Education**

City University of Hong Kong | Hong Kong Bachelor of Computer Science | 05/2020